{
    "subject": "resource/Peter_Shor",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Putnam_Fellows",
    "human_readable": "Peter Shor is the subject of Category:Putnam Fellows.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8721961379051208,
            "question": "When did Peter Shor receive the Putnam Fellowship?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7334431409835815,
            "question": "Who is Peter Shor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6975599527359009,
            "question": "What is a Putnam Fellow?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5582788586616516,
            "question": "What does it mean to be a Putnam Fellow?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5498729944229126,
            "question": "In what field of study is Peter Shor recognized?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4896295666694641,
            "question": "Is Peter Shor known for any significant achievements?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4705323874950409,
            "question": "What are some characteristics of a successful Putnam Fellow?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4436620771884918,
            "question": "Are there any other notable individuals who have been Putnam Fellows?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4210055470466614,
            "question": "How does being a Putnam Fellow impact one's career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2994692325592041,
            "question": "What prestigious award did Peter Shor receive?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Peter Shor is the subject of Category:Putnam Fellows.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2449_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How does being a Putnam Fellow impact one's career?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2449_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any other notable individuals who have been Putnam Fellows?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2449_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some characteristics of a successful Putnam Fellow?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2449_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2449_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2449_107.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2449_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2449_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2449_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2449_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2449_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2449_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2449_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2449_82.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because the documents provided contain information about Peter Shor being a Putnam Fellow, as mentioned in the text from file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_2449/re-ranker-msmarco/126.txt."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nExplanation: The documents provide information about Peter Shor's achievements, including his involvement as a Putnam Fellow while an undergraduate student at Caltech and mentions that current MIT math professors who were Putnam Fellows include him. This supports the statement that Peter Shor is the subject of the Category:Putnam Fellows."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}